all right so if this video gets anywhere
from 2 000 to 3 000 likes and let's say
500 comments we'll get him back on a
part two so
what's up guys welcome back to how to
teach a McDonald's employee part two
well McDonald's right if you guys
haven't seen part one make sure to go
check it out like the amount of love the
amount of energy I got from my last
video is just it's fun to say like I've
never gotten that much energy in my DMs
and comments like it's just insane right
like the things that I got in the
comments privately is like insane and
due to all of your guys's feedback not
only am I doing part two with Josh now
but I got something coming for every
single one of you guys same way how I'm
giving back to Josh right now I'm gonna
do to every single one of you guys I
found the New Passion like a new
pleasure with inside of me and it's like
giving back to you guys because one
thing is like this life style like my
normal whatever the partying the cars
like the money like all of this is like
my normal but giving somebody else a
taste of it it gives me a different type
of pleasure seeing them like seeing
their smile seeing how that now they're
motivated to continue working towards
the girls or whatever the case is like
that is my new passion and honestly like
you can I can legit change somebody's
life
so that is my neat drive now so I got
something coming to every single one of
you guys watching this video obviously
if you want to put in the work um what
I'm gonna give you guys every single one
of you guys a taste of what it is in
this lifestyle what is capable obviously
consistency so um we got Josh now uh I
told him to pull up to the level of HQ
but then I had remembered I was like oh
like last video when you pulled up he
was like all sweaty and dirty from work
so I'm like bro go home don't even worry
about it I'm gonna go pick you up the
shower after I pick you up we're gonna
go back to the level of HQ and then I'm
just gonna show you kind of what I
figured that I left out on last video
because I feel like the last video we
went straight into technicals which is
good because obviously like without
seeing the charts you're not gonna do
anything you need to know how to
properly read the charts but there's
five key principles that you need to
know before you get into the charts to
obviously succeed to trading so that's
exactly what I'm going to teach in this
video so make sure to watch the video
all the way to the end if you guys like
trust me all you have to do in this
video just like comment and subscribe
for either a part three I definitely
want to do a part three of Josh but
before the part three I want to give
back to you guys so like exactly what
I'm doing with Josh to every single
single like comment subscribe literally
so now we're gonna go pick up Josh take
him back to the level of HQ I think it's
his first time in Alamo I don't think
he's ever been in a Lambo in his life
um so we're gonna go crazy I don't have
a GoPro outside it's kind of whack I
wanted to get
traffic and stuff so after that we're
gonna go to the HQ and I'm gonna teach
you the five things that he needs before
the technical music they're very key
principles
[Music]
this guy gonna pick me up
this is all-wheel drive oh that's why I
feel so different holy [__] because he
can't do a 20 wrong because he has real
wheel drive so he'll just spin out this
[__] for weird
thank you
I just took him around like you know
like the where the hoop is like the Park
yeah for like 130 140. this guy's like
sweating 131. kilometers
so update on the certificate wall
um
last time you guys were here it was
empty because we were working on it then
I got full but we've been putting like
some loud ass music and I guess the the
tape isn't sticking so some of you guys
have leveled down I'm sorry I'm sorry we
will make sure you level up again let's
show them show them
sorry guys trust me I will make it mine
power my what would I make in my what
you do it my duty so you guys level up
again
um all right you ready so last time we
had here Josh kind of like I already
told you guys like we took him straight
to the technicals which is dope
obviously you need to know technicals
how to trade but like there's a couple
key factors like before you trade that
you need to have like it's like before
you go to to battle like you need to
have your specific gear then you're
ready to fight it's kind of the same
thing like we're gonna armor him now
with the things he needs in order to
succeed so when he goes out to battle he
has the right strategy on how to shank
somebody or whatever oh yeah tell them
about the trade yeah yeah so
um I mean pretty much
it was like it was a very simple trade
and I had some hints and clues from like
looking over what was going on with the
stocks like I was able to go through the
news or whatever and um I just had
noticed that it was bouncing off like a
certain resistance point and so in that
I was just looking for what he showed me
and I kind of wanted to take what he
showed me and show you guys that it's
possible so I wanted to apply it into my
own like you know my own portfolio my
own way of working so I went ahead and I
looked for exactly what he showed me
which was previous resistance Point uh
following Trend and then obviously uh
buy-in signals or uh for in this case
it's uh bearish engulfing and I found
every single one so I took the trade but
unfortunately I put my stop losses too
short so when it came back to retake
regain uh buyers it stopped me out
but but the trade did fall through and
it did go as planned so I'm happy about
that and it made me more confident all
right [__] happens we'll get you to not
miss this train yeah all right so now
that we're here at the computer we're
gonna set him up with like the gear that
he needs in order to succeed right and
like he has no idea what I'm about to
give him
um he's like you're like what are we
gonna film so like I'm prepared I'm like
bro don't worry about it like just
natural this [__] out right so first
things first
um this is the uh broker that I use and
um I'm gonna be funding him a thousand
dollars right so I'm going to be giving
you a thousand dollars to trade
completely all of me like so you can
blow that [__] you can't don't withdraw
it like don't go to strip club I guess
and then you do whatever you want with
it right so then this is the broker that
I use but like the broker that I use is
gonna credit him right because then you
guys asked me like how do I get access
to a lot more Capital you could either
go the funded route or you can use the
broker that I use and then if you sign
up with the link below
um they give you access to a credit so
now I'm gonna give them now a thousand
dollars and then the broker is going to
credit him 50 from the Thousand so now
you're gonna have a code like a total of
like a thousand five hundred completely
for free so I'm gonna give you a
thousand the broker's gonna give you um
500 bucks extra inches right the only
way to do it is you have to sign up
through the link under
um you go to open up a live account
you select whatever account you want
into for mt5 and then when you go to
continue you select whatever size you
want and then
um oh wait you have to go back to
category it has to be mt5 you click
continue and then you have to click
bonus account so in this bonus account
you just you know do whatever leverage
you want whatever the case is you can
see right here the first transfer of
your account you'll receive 50 to match
this to credit whatever so I'm gonna
deposit you a thousand dollars into your
account
um I'm gonna put you at a one to 500
leverage so basically like you're 1500
bucks like you can trade like if it were
to be a lot more which is crazy it's not
like stocks because when it's stocks
like they cut your leverage you need to
have a lot of access to a lot more
Capital so the only way to do this is
you guys have to sign up to the link
below and then you basically do your
whole entire kyc procedure whatever and
then they give you access to this bonus
account if you guys need any help or if
you guys want more bonus just go to the
live chat and just type FX Alex G
um and they'll help you out so this is
first things first you're going to have
a free thousand dollars to drink like
completely on me right and then 500 on
the broker but then like I feel like
trading is hard and then it's going to
get to the point where like like you're
still learning right in order for you to
make money on by yourself it's gonna
take you I would say like definitely
like I'm shorting your learning curve by
like a year like 100 like 100 so let's
give it another year so it's the same so
I I say maybe like Q3 at next year so
that's maybe like six to eight months
you could do this [__] on your own yeah
so now I'm gonna set you up with the
account are you gonna have the money but
obviously I don't want you to go in and
like blow it correct so I have signals
so like you can do like copy the trades
that I take so I'm like on a winning
streak right now like two week winning
streak um I've made about like 25 like
I'll pop up a screenshot right here 25
in two weeks so let's do the math so
let's say if you would have just copied
my signals from the 1500 books I can do
a math for you all right so what is it
it'll be uh 200 250 that'd be uh 325
000. just make sure no 275 plus times 25
so if you just copy my signals like
you're gonna make free money so I'm just
gonna throw you in the chat
um there's a free app so pull out your
phone so you download yeah
when we were hauling ass to like stick
that out of this bucket so I'm gonna say
I'm gonna set you up so first things
first I'm gonna give you the 1500 bucks
and Philly on me I got you second thing
is I'm gonna set you up with the signals
because I don't want you just to like go
on here and just take a couple trades
for sure that's pointless like I want
you to make money from the money so step
two is I'm gonna give you access to my
signals for free that you can just go on
there I'll show you how to set up
everything you know you're gonna aren't
you starting a signals group this week
yeah yeah so I would be yeah so you're
ready yeah yeah so I mean you're good
like I just I'm gonna get your email get
your access to the signals and then step
three like when you're copying these
signals obviously like when we go over
to like trading View and then like I
want you to whenever I send a signal
group I mean whenever I send the signal
in the signal group I want you to go to
the Chart whether it's on your phone or
whatever the case is look at the pair
and I want you to take a screenshot of
the train when you take a screenshot of
the trade within the app there's a
section that is like uh kind of like
your own you could Journey your own
trades so like you build your own track
record whether you take the trade or not
so in the app I want you to take a
screenshot and then you need to Journey
your trades because if you're not
joining them like you're not going to
learn from your machine yeah exactly
like so every single time you take a
trade you're going to screenshot it and
put it in your journey So then whenever
you're done with the signals or you want
to start taking your own trades you look
back and you're like holy [__] like
we've been taking the same trade time
and time after again kind of like how
you mentioned that you took your trade
yeah so it's basically the same thing
right so that'd be step three so first
thing the money second thing I'm gonna
make you money by just copying
everything that I do so if you guys want
to get access to my app it's just
literally click the link below or search
it up it's on the Apple store or on
Android it's a swing trading lab it's
free I drop a free signal and the free
uh section every once in a while there's
a Physicians guys calculator in there uh
stuff
um so three years bro I'm telling you
you've got gotta Journey your trades
like probably like one of the things
that set me aside was like for myself
right like I don't really compete with
anybody or at least I don't anymore like
I don't compare myself to anybody
anymore like I just look at myself like
I look at my results and who I am as a
person
every single two weeks so I'm like all
right how much of a shitty person was I
this week yes how much of a good person
yeah and every single week I try to get
but that's why I'm doing videos like
this you know trying to help you out
like the best that I can because I want
to like not only improve me but try to
improve people around me like it's like
a new form of pleasure to me yeah which
is like you know dope so it comes to the
same exact thing where you're treating
like if you're not draining the trade
you're taking then it's how do you know
you're getting better or not I mean like
for example let's say right now you work
your electricity job right so you said
you have a box yeah okay is there
somebody above your boss yeah the owner
so then it's you the boss and the owner
well it's me the guy who kind of runs me
tells me who to work with and then the
boss of like the construction site and
then the owner okay is there anybody
under here no not yet for example when
you do electricity like does anybody
have to set anything up for you
so when you [__] up at the bottom yeah
there's somebody holding like you got
people on top of you holding you
accountable right okay when it comes to
Trading
you are every single person in that
chain like you have to hold yourself
accountable for everything for example
let's say right now in trading there is
a section so what's what's your section
in your job like what do you do
I'm an electrician okay but like
electricity is like Baseline like you're
working employee yeah but like like you
set up chords like what do you do so run
wires Bend pipes kind of set everything
up and then kind of they'll come look at
your work but they tell you what to do
like oh I need this pipeline here from
here to here I need this pipe thrown
into this but into this box with uh
three live cables uh obviously a ground
and a neutral so then after you do the
work somebody come and supervises
correct so you would come and look at it
and then what is the boss and then the
boss kind of like if this or the
yeah then the boss would review it but
the boss wouldn't revealed right away
you would kind of look at your work when
when um when before inspection and then
the owner just doesn't do [__] no
it's all yeah okay so you see how
there's a change everything so when it
comes to trading there is the same exact
chain just you're the only person going
to hold yourself accountable for
everything so let's say you [__] up
right now and you don't put the ground
then the positive negative whoever you
[__] electrocute everybody and you
just Zack though you just have the whole
place they're gonna like like you're
done they're gonna put your head up in
training there is the same exact
precaution that you're not gonna zap
anybody's head off you're just gonna
blow your account or you're just gonna
like do damage to your psychology
because there's nobody on top of you
holding yourself accountable yeah so you
need to play every single one of those
roles to trading so when it comes to
trading plan you're holding yourself
accountable when it comes to risk
management you're holding yourself when
it comes to entry signals you're holding
yourself a camera when it comes to
holding the trade you're holding this
yourself like there's so many people
like I mean there's so many things you
have to do that's why as a Trader it's
very hard is that where your strategy
like comes yeah so like having your
strategy like just shortens out of that
[__] and then it just puts everything in
one and then like you need to understand
that you're that one person yeah I mean
people don't understand that that's why
like the community like Community stuff
that's how we like that's why we're
building level up is that we want to
have a person for every single one of
these things so it's not too much on one
person like trading alone is very hard
right so I'm just like telling what
everything that I'm gonna set you up now
it's just going to be easier for you to
manage all these things yeah but you
need to Journey your things well
drinking it I'm telling you bro it's
going to be very difficult and then the
last thing which is going to be Point
number well not the last thing the point
number four
is going to be the
Candlestick pipe right it's kind of like
what I was telling you earlier in the
car like breeding the market is cool but
then you need to learn how to like for
example when you're journaling your
trades you're going to notice time and
time again like you're like damn bro
like Alex took the same trade every
single day at the same time with the
same Candlestick and if you notice if
you read the Candlestick Bible there's
entry signals there's certain rejections
certain engulfings that I look for on
specific time frames that the only way
you're going to know it is obviously if
you're journaling your trades but before
you Journal them you got to learn how to
read them so I'm gonna give you access
to the Candlestick Bible it helps you
what grade candles yeah yeah yeah so
like like let me show you like kind of
like a little sneak peek right here
I think it's free bro I don't know why
people like take itself crazy Bible
right so this is the Candlestick Bible
book yeah I think it's free like you
could just preview it right here but I'm
gonna give you access it I have the PDF
just gonna email it to you this trade is
honestly the trade that may I mean this
is the the book that made me in trading
because it teaches you how to read the
camera sticks if you're not reading
candlesticks like this is something that
I talked about in the garage I talked
about it could pop up like a little clip
of uh the like when Roger was talking
about the pie chart you can throw
indicators on the charts notes just
gotta read the charts right
um and then there's another book which
this for me honestly was the book that
set me aside as a traitor when it comes
to psychology and it's trading in the
Zone by Mark Douglas that you're not
ready for this book yet but you still
haven't experience like you know like
you're telling me you break controllers
when you play COD yeah and you blow an
account it's a lot worse bro yeah
like you're gonna break your phone
whenever the people and break so it's
the same exact thing but imagine a book
that whenever you're playing card or
whatever like it would teach you how to
avoid that it's the same exact thing
this book is that psychology of trading
for me if you guys are kind of in that
stage where you guys already have gone
through the you know the Candlestick
Bible so on and so forth this is your
next book to to basically read like this
is literally going to tell you how you
feel every single day you trade and how
to manage it so for me this is the book
that I feel like you're not ready yet
for I would say maybe six months in and
you break a couple phones blow a couple
accounts hopefully not the 1500 but this
is going to be the thing that's going to
set you aside so I mean these are four
key factors that you need to trade you
need Capital to trade so I'm hooking you
up and then the broker's gonna hook you
up as well signals so you start making
money right away hopefully you get the
[__] out of electricity or work less you
know work a little bit less
um three you gotta Journal your things
without journaling you're not gonna know
what you're doing wrong you're not going
to hold yourself accountable and then
four set you up with the right book so
read right because there's no point of
reading a book that's not trading
related like we're in the business of
trading right and then for the fifth
point which is um something different
nobody's ever seen
um I'm sure you're gonna put Doyle is
Right Doyle yeah Doyle so doyo is um
he's a Trader and he used to work at
Amazon so I'm gonna like like he's gonna
pull up now like this guy's very known
very famous as well on YouTube like
Doyle is somebody that was working on
Amazon delivering things I believe
correct me if I'm wrong and he just
became a consistently profit as a Trader
maybe like a year and a half two years
ago he was living in Chicago just doing
his thing and now he's a full-time
Trader here in Miami like full-time I
think he worked at the airport something
that I don't know man my bad daughter I
don't I don't really know man but like
to my point is he was just like a
regular guy yeah so like I want him to
come in and I just want him to talk to
you like some psychology things or like
some things that helped him leave work
because I could talk to you about like
my experience but I actually want to
hear his experience because we're going
to do a podcast now too so you're gonna
get like first point of view of the
podcast all right so it's gonna be it's
gonna be pretty dope so um those are the
five things like honestly I want to do
this to every single one of you guys out
there all you have to do is just like
comment and subscribe I want to do a
part three with Josh I want to say in
like like 30 days right because this is
for sure like a month yeah yeah because
that'll give you enough time to [__] up
the account and like I I've been
researching Forex since I used to do
stocks and forks you can trade all day
yeah so all I do is have to set up a
time period where I'm available I mean
I'm going to school and everything but I
can definitely set up you know some time
aside to be able to sit down Place
trades and at work I play Streets
sometimes whenever you know a trade
comes up I mean the more volatile times
are going to be New York and then London
there's gonna be the two times where
like the market moves the most so London
is like middle of the night New York is
like beginning in the morning so you can
either get a trade before you go to
sleep yeah yeah and then ride all week
yeah
yeah it's easy yeah well I I've been
looking at you seven forget that's a
good thing because I always put my stop
loss and then I'm always gonna check my
phone check my phone
I'm like that I can't put this [__] down
together
um Chad Dora's probably gonna pull up in
like 20 or 30 minutes we're gonna go
play some ping pong while he gets here
and
um 30 days I'm gonna give him all these
you know tips I'm gonna throw him in the
chat with my other Traders and the guys
just take care of Josh because I really
want to like I really want to see if
like this one-on-one experience I can
love him give the [__] up and then I
want to do with a group of you guys as
well so um stay tuned so let's wait now
for Dory to pull up
yeah no yeah we're gonna do a group very
soon very very soon and then I'm like oh
like [__] man like this shit's getting
annoying like nobody wants to make two
300 bucks in like five minutes and then
like nobody wanted to do it nobody bro
I'm like yo just come outside everybody
thought it was his Camp yeah everybody I
mean bro I mean bro where when are
Rolls-Royce in the middle of a
drive-through with a big ass camera like
this like everybody's intimidated so
then I was just like bro [__] man like I
was literally gonna call it a day call
it a video and then we're leaving uh
Starbucks drive-through and I see this
guy walking through the car I'm like bro
that's that's the guy that's that's good
I'm going to make 200 bucks like I mean
yeah [__] Eddie just got in Bros
he's so nervous he drops
I had my because I was at work I had my
knife right here so I knew I was
chilling
like a stabbed in the video
no no so I mean like I wanted you to
give him some some tips bro like what
did you do to get you from like Detroit
to like now living in Miami like this
different lifestyle from what used to be
living so like what was it that changed
it for you because I already told him
what I did but I wanted you to come in
and then kind of give him like some tips
and I wanted him to have like front row
seat of the podcast we're about to do
your your followers have been driving me
crazy for the podcast man like every
single video I dropped get Doyle I'm
like bro coming soon coming soon so this
is the perfect time so I mean what would
you tell to the boy Joshua
um well well really like took my
training to the next level was I mean
obviously I knew the strategy like I had
my strategy down back
the planet man that's my bread and
butter but it was really just me
believing that I can do this like full
time because you see people on the
internet they say oh you could do this
to do that but then when you be in like
behind the chart by yourself like it's a
whole different like it's just
completely different so I really had to
get my mindset right to like okay is
this even possible and once I um
saw that I was able to like double
accounts uh triple accounts then I was
like okay I think I can really do this
full time so it was really just me just
getting my mindset right to be able to
yeah okay so at first I was trading New
York session no no actually at first I
was trading London sessions and then I'm
like okay this is kind of messing up my
sleeping schedule now London session is
around 3 A.M Eastern Standard Time and
um it was hard for me to wake up and
like focus on getting getting my trades
and and like staying up the entire
session so I'm like okay I gotta make a
sacrifice so I have to go to second
shift and trade in the morning so that's
literally what I did so 8 A.M to like
noon I would trade I'll study a little
bit after and then after that I go to
work get off of work around like
midnight study a little bit more do it
again I had to just keep doing that so I
can throw my account and um add more
money to it so like yeah it was a grind
bro but I just I didn't have no choice
like this or work a job so you know what
I'm saying but absolutely what I had to
do yeah for sure yeah and like and like
did you did when you when you were when
you were doing that like when did it
finally like you feel me like all right
I gotta quit I gotta go
um when I was able to like get my
account passed like 40 50 000 without me
adding no money to it because like like
At first I saved up like 15K I was just
trading throwing money into it I was in
college at the time too so I was getting
refund checks I'm throwing that in there
I'm working like I'm just saving my
money because I don't really have a lot
of bills at that time I was like in my
apartment out of college it was like
expensive it was super low so I was able
to say it so I was fortunate enough to
have
um my Fields be super low so I can save
so once I got 15K I'm like okay can I
double this can I make can I make it
into 30k then once I got a 30k I'm like
okay let me see if I can do this one
more time without adding money to it
that was just the key like can I just do
this without adding no more money to it
so that's really what took me to the
next level of me actually doubling my
account yeah so I'm okay I can do this
yeah
so and then I kind of like a little like
like
preview to like the podcast like why
like why am I like why'd you come to
Miami
I mean
um if Detroit is your hometown
I mean honestly I just wanted something
different
um I definitely came here to like
Network a little bit like I just wanted
to be around like-minded people like me
because I mean I'm a day trader but I'm
really an entrepreneur so I like getting
into other stuff so people in Detroit it
wasn't really a lot of people like that
like they really just wanted to work a
job so that's why I had to leave yeah so
like it would just be
um it was a networking move for me and I
just enjoyed Miami like it's just lit
being here I just I really just love
being here so
all right yeah so now what would you
like what would you say is like the next
step Josh should do that right so he's
working right now full-time electrician
he's just been 15 days non-stop like no
weekends off nothing right I know
weekends off no they March 15 day 15 to
the end of this week till Friday Friday
will be my first day well Saturday so
how are you going to have time to yeah
like you gotta you gotta make time like
there's no other way so what are you
going to do I mean what what why I've
been doing for now is whenever I do have
time at work
um we get 15 minute breaks like every
two hours time because I work like uh
electricity so I mean some people are
under a union and unions have to give
you 15 minute breaks like every two
hours yeah something like have to so
every time I have a 15 minute break I
just sit on my phone and watch like
other stuff that I'm watching right now
is I only focus on one stop because
advice I've taken from people is Google
so I just sit there and watch Google all
day five minute chart 15 30 minutes and
four hours so you're not out really
putting a lot of time into trading yeah
and then I got home and I watched I've
gone over some of my Havoc videos so
when you get home how much time do you
have I put about an hour oh oh I have
only an hour to put into it as of right
now yeah because I go to school or you
go to school too yeah it was tough
that's right that's why I'm saying I
don't know what it was like like what
does he do I work like that's really odd
that your window you only have an hour
what else can you do like you don't have
like you gotta put time in this yeah
yeah if it's only just one hour you
gotta make the best of that one hour so
like what exactly are you like doing in
that that's that's what I was actually
gonna ask Alex today kind of how to
structure my day about going like like
should I should I go through my my
should I go to the stock that I'm
watching obviously I'm gonna try and go
over the forest as Alex is gonna fund my
account and stuff so I found it yeah I
gave it 1500 bucks so I'm just like
blush just [__] burn it
yeah I'm gonna try not to lose
you're probably gonna lose it but it's
just it's a learning curve yeah so like
even when you lose it don't get
discouraged yeah it's gonna happen yeah
everybody lose money and I told him I'm
like look like I want you to because I
wanted to read trading in the zone but
I'm like you're not ready for that yet
like you don't know yeah that's what I'm
saying I'm just like you're not like you
don't understand what like the
psychology part I mean he's only in it
for like three four weeks maybe a month
and with stocks right so when we bring
them over to foreign
but he gets the technicals though like
he like like we've been talking about
just technicals and then like the
technicals that I taught him he's
implementing in the stocks which is kind
of cool I don't know you can you know
yeah use the same strategy for
everything yeah
um but like kind of what like I want to
structure him now he's like bro if all
you have is like an hour a day just
literally probably like you can't trade
in an hour there's literally nothing you
can do and probably the hour you have
probably like Sydney Tokyo like there's
not much movement so I would just say
just like bro literally watch every
single video you can just consume that
information and then just because it's
chart time I think in a day today
it's a swing trading yeah because if you
only have an hour
that's what I've been doing
yeah I only take one to two days periods
okay yeah yeah yeah
so now we're gonna do like a part three
but in 30 days so I'm gonna give him
everything the 1500 bucks can count
everything and then in 30 days I want to
see where he's at did you blow the shade
how you got it better like talk to me
now about trading I don't want you I
don't want to talk to you about trading
I want you to talk to me so then we'll
see kind of how I go so I mean like I
mean you know if you got some time I
mean so basically what would be your
best tip you to give
um
okay you got money you kind of
understand the concept of trading
um I would say
to give 30 minutes of
watching educational videos and then 30
minutes of actually back testing the
strategy that you're trying to learn
because you only got an hour so 30
minutes of watching educational videos
and then 30 minutes of applying it
seeing like can you see the setups or um
if you want to like simulate the
strategy whatever you use like just
simulate that but that's really all
you're going to have to do with the plot
is it like it's it's you'll learn more
when you actually trade when the
Market's open but since you're like
coming in and it's just gonna be back
testing and watching videos it's gonna
be kind of hard for you you're learning
curve to like accelerate but like you're
gonna be good though but definitely like
I don't know how you're gonna have to
change some schedules so like you're
gonna have to like you're gonna have to
the thing about school also is that I'd
be like I be on my phone you know just
going on and I I don't use my phone for
like social media like if I'm on my
phone I'm either look I'm dead ass
looking at your hearts or just like
watching like or reading I like to read
a lot of like uh the Wall Street Journal
and stuff like that okay so I'm always
trying to like keep myself updated with
what's going on okay yeah yeah
definitely you got to utilize that one
hour let's see let's see what it is bro
appreciate you bro appreciate you coming
in yes sir trust me like the pressure is
on you yeah yeah yeah
hey what's your name bro Josh his name
is Josh bro y'all gonna see him in a few
years
the podcast now yeah do the podcast all
right all right so make sure to like
comment subscribe and then after we do
the podcast we'll go eat and we'll get
some shots of going to go you want to
race you want a ride yeah come on now
you're gonna beat me bro come on man